Better hide well, or your hair will show.
[SUMBAKꓘOKJIL]
Anyone who wants to play hide and seek, gather here.
[A late night wrapped in darkness]
[The school where all the students disappeared]
[Echoing through that place]
[A mysterious sound]
Please, please.
What is that sound?
Stay calm.
Wait a second.
Ha, wait a second.
I'm scared.
This is seriously scary.
I think I might cry.
No one's here?
No one?
I want to go home.
(Everyone) Stay alive.
[If you want to survive]
[You must hide well]
Hey! Hey! It’s coming! It’s coming!
[Once the game starts]
[It can never be stopped]
[SUMBAKꓘOKJIL]
Where am I?
It’s so bright.
[(Just a slight smile)]
Where is this place?
[NCT WISH woke up in different places]
What am I supposed to do?
Really? No one’s here?
What is this?
[Phone found hanging on the neck]
[Phone notification sound]
Whoa, that scared me.
Hm?
What is this?
What is this.
[Phone operation sound]
Hm?
I think I pressed something wrong.
"Find the school supplies with the members' names on them."
"If caught by the seeker, by using the school supplies"
"You can escape just once."
[Heavy breathing]
This is scarier than I thought.
What is this even?
I want to go home.
Let’s go.
(The place I was in) was the locker room.
School supplies?
Seriously.
[Special effect sound]
Whoa, that scared me.
What's with the smoke?
For real.
[Trap]
[A rough start for JAEHEE]
Hold on.
I really hate this.
[Checking the outside situation]
[Back to position]
[Practice building 1F SION / 2F YUSHI / 3F RIKU]
[Learning building 1F SAKUYA / 2F JAEHEE / 3F RYO]
[Sound of door opening]
I'm scared.
Scared.
Wait a second.
What is this?
Can I go this way?
[YUSHI]
[Going up to the 3rd floor of the practice building]
Ugh, I'm scared.
What do I do...
[RIKU is on the 3rd floor]
[RIKU →]
What are you doing?
I don't know.
I'm really scared.
I'm scared.
Maybe I should just stay here?
I'm so scared x3.
[Trap]
Whoa, that scared me.
[1st floor of the learning building]
I really hate this.
[Another person gripped by fear]
Wait, wait, wait x4
I really hate this.
What should I do, seriously.
I hate this so much. Seriously hate it.
This won’t do.
I seriously can't.
[SAKUYA picks up chopsticks]
[Carefully steps out with courage]
What the!
[SAKUYA →]
[Luckily spots the members]
What's that?
[(Chopsticks of courage)]
What does school supplies mean?
Stuff like pencils.
That's what we’re supposed to find.
The ones with our names on them.
If we find the school supplies, we can escape when we get caught.
[(Nods)]
[The three move together]
[(Go ahead first)]
What is this?
[Special effect sound]
[Uable to watch any longer, YUSHI takes the lead]
[RYO, RIKU, YUSHI]
[Moving from the practice building to the learning building through a connected path]
- It's a stage, a stage. Like a performance stage.
- Fighting!
[3rd floor of the learning building / JAEHEE]
[JAEHEE wandering alone]
[Sighs]
Hold on.
[Meets RYO who couldn’t get out of the classroom]
Where are you going?
Don’t grab me!
I said don’t!
[← Someone is approaching]
[RIKU, who was downstairs, joins]
What’s so scary?
Wait, is there really a seeker?
No, it’s just...
That text from earlier...
Wait, don’t open the door.
Are we not supposed to go in here?
I don’t know.
It’s fine to go in here.
We have to find the school supplies.
Go inside here.
Why are you sending me alone?
What’s so scary about this?
Why these two?
How do I put this on silent mode?
[SION switches his phone to silent mode first]
I need to find a place to hide.
Somewhere to hide…
It’s way too visible here.
There’s nothing.
Oh it's here.
[Something catches SION’s eye]
[← Compass]
It’s RIKU’s.
[Finds RIKU’s compass]
[Practice building 2F SION]
[SION speeds up after finding a school supply item]
I only found one.
What is this? It’s kinda cute.
Popcorn, spicy noodles, honey butter, a thousand won?
I should write ‘NCT WISH was here’ on this.
[(Everyone, fighting)]
[SION refocuses on finding school supplies]
Let’s just find it first!
[Did he just find something?]
What the.
[A business card with an unfamiliar name]
So that’s what it was. It was a business card.
Where could the school supplies be?
[Three people in the 3rd floor science lab of the learning building / JAEHEE, RYO, RIKU]
To find school supplies.
But there aren't any.
There’s nothing, guys.
What do we do?
[Still haven't found a single school supply]
But the place to solve that question is on the floor below, Class 7, Grade 3.
I went in there, where to solve the question...
[Everyone freezes at a nearby sound]
[Is someone nearby?]
[Learning building 3F: JAEHEE, RYO, RIKU / YUSHI]
Sorry.
[The culprit is YUSHI, on the same floor]
[A small sound causes big confusion]
[Phone notification sound]
[Hint]
What is this?
Scissors?
Where is this?
These are stairs.
Stairs, stairs.
[After checking the hint, they head out]
It’s in front of the stairs.
[But]
[The scissors are already with SION]
This one’s RYO’s.
So they’re hidden like this?
[Obtain RYO's scissors]
[The other three still don’t know this]
Stairs, stairs.
[Heading to the stairs]
- It’s in front of the stairs.
- Hold on.
I’ll go in the middle, I’ll go in the middle.
I’m in the middle...
I’m in the middle, I’m in the middle.
(At first) where did you come from?
Wait, don’t grab me.
[Phone notification sound]
Where from? From over there?
[Hint]
Isn’t this the science lab?
If it’s the science lab, isn’t this here?
[Could the school supplies be in the science lab they stayed in so long?]
- Isn’t it here?
- It’s here, it’s here.
Isn’t it here?
It’s here.
[Obtains SAKUYA's eraser]
SAKUYA x6
Give this to SAKUYA.
We have to give this to SAKUYA.
Let’s wait for SAKUYA here, let’s wait here.
No, we should move.
[RYO settles inside a cabinet]
Earlier, we were hiding in the locker.
Let’s wait here.
Let’s look for SAKUYA.
SAKUYA is right below.
Let’s find SAKUYA first.
[RIKU and JAEHEE head toward SAKUYA]
I told you, we were hiding in a place like this earlier.
Sakuya’s right below.
[Learning building 2F: SAKUYA]
So this is what it is, it’s the scissors.
[SAKUYA checking the hint on the 2nd floor of the learning building]
What is this?
So we just have to find this, right?
I'm not scared of anything.
Yeah, well...
Yeah, I’m just doing it.
[Phone notification sound]
Whoa, that scared me.
So loud x4
[Also checking the eraser hint]
So what is this?
Yeah, well, I mean, yeah.
Yeah, well...
What...
Well...
I'm not scared at all.
Yeah, I’m just doing it, yeah.
It might not be fun, but whatever.
Just, you know...
I just go, right?
I just do it.
Whoa! That scared me.
(Director) Sorry.
[JAEHEE’s voice from upstairs]
[The moment JAEHEE let his guard down]
Hello.
[Surprised the moment JAEHEE let his guard down]
SAKUYA! SAKUYA!
It’s Sakuya’s! It’s Sakuya’s!
Huh?
Really?
[The eraser finds its rightful owner]
[SION joins after hearing JAEHEE scream]
JAEHEE! JAEHEE!
Huh?
Did you find mine?
No, not yet.
You didn’t find even one school supply?
Nope.
I found Sakuya’s.
You found Sakuya’s?
Anyone find mine?
Nope.
No one?
I already found three school supplies.
- Already?
- How did you find them?
[Practice building 3F SION]
[SION found the compass and scissors]
Huh? What’s this?
[← Secret pen / Another school supply found]
JAEHEE.
Everything’s being found except mine.
[JAEHEE’s secret pen obtained]
[School supplies returning to their owners]
- RIKU.
- This is mine?
RYO, is that Sakuya’s?
Where’s mine?
No idea. I didn’t find mine either.
YUSHI, let’s look for it with me.
Did you guys see that?
That globe hint?
The globe one is Sakuya’s.
[While checking the found school supplies]
- That’s Sakuya’s?
- Yeah.
[YUSHI suddenly gets startled alone]
Oh my gosh.
[Turn the other way and do it again]
He gets scared so easily.
Why are they so cute though?
Nothing on the upper floor?
- Nothing upstairs.
- There’s nothing on the upper floor.
We need to hurry up and go find them now.
[Phone notification sound]
We got a message.
RYO, did you find yours?
I found RYO’s.
[Hint]
- “Save the Earth.”
- Where is this place?
“Save the Earth.”
Did you check everything here?
We have been upstairs.
Haven’t checked here yet?
Then I’ll go check this area.
[NCT WISH splits up]
Isn’t it here?
Why is it so dark though?
It’s so dark.
We haven’t found ours yet.
I’ve already found three of the others’.
But I haven’t found ours.
[SION ? / RIKU: compass / YUSHI ?]
[JAEHEE: secret pen / RYO: scissors / SAKUYA: eraser]
[The frequency calling for the school supplies]
We need to find SION's.
No.
[RYO, who was alone, sets out after seeing the hint]
I wanna go.
[Everyone doing their best to find the school supplies]
What the? “Save the Earth” x3
What? x3
“Save the Earth.”
[(Freezes)]
Is it here?
Why, what's going on? What is it?
Why x3
[SAKUYA senses something strange]
[JAEHEE spots something too?]
[← Poster from the hint]
“Save the Earth.”
It’s here.
[A protractor stuck on the poster]
[The moment he carefully peeled off]
Got it.
[A full-powered scream]
Now I'm the seeker.
Better hide well, or your hair will show.
[Hide-and-seek begins]
[The seeker awakens from inside the poster]
Better hide well, or your hair will show.
[RYO is on the 3rd floor of the practice building]
Better hide well.
[(Confused)]
I see your clothes peeking out.
[YUSHI hides in the lab across the hall]
Hey, hide! x3
[Practice building 3F: RYO, RIKU, YUSHI]
Better hide well.
[RIKU rushes into a nearby lab]
I see RIKU.
[JAEHEE, who came down last]
Hey, hide! x3
[← RYO]
[Accidentally meets up with RYO]
[SAKUYA and SION also on 2F of the practice building]
[Practice building 3F: RYO, JAEHEE, RIKU, YUSHI]
[2F: SAKUYA, SION]
[Will they be able to finish the game safely?]
[Remaining time for hide-and-seek]
[← RYO]
[← JAEHEE]
I found SION’s school supply.
[← SION’s protractor]
SION’s.
RYO, RYO, RYO!
I saw a ghost earlier.
A ghost?
A ghost!
Right when I took it out, a face popped out.
Isn’t that the seeker?
Are you saying the seeker is a ghost?
[Phone notification sound]
[(Surprised)]
Why is this so scary, seriously?
"Hide-and-seek starts now."
"The game time is 4,444 seconds."
Why is it 4,444 seconds.
"If you get caught by the seeker, you’ll immediately be trapped somewhere."
"Hide-and-seek is a game where survival rate is very important."
"If the survival rate is over 50%, NCTzens will receive a big reward."
"So please do your best to hide well."
So that means
(If over 50%) three people.
We just need three people left, then.
Okay, okay.
Czennie, wait for us.
[The seeker starts moving]
[Height almost reaching the ceiling]
So scary, so scary.
Who is it?
[Those who must hide]
[And the one who must seek]
[What will be the result of this survival game?]
[Practice building 3rd floor]
[↓ YUSHI]
[3F: JAEHEE, RYO / 2F: YUSHI]
It’s been ages since I played hide-and-seek.
The last time I played hide-and-seek
I think it was about six years ago.
Six years ago? How old was I then?
So elementary school was the last time.
[While YUSHI reminisces about the past]
I should check somewhere else.
Why?
I need to find SION.
[JAEHEE, anxious about SION]
- Where did SION go?
- I don’t know.
What the x3
[Steps on a trap and returns to starting point]
[RIKU →]
[RIKU moves to a classroom on the 2nd floor of the learning building]
This is seriously scary.
What do I do?
[Practice building 2F / SION / SAKUYA]
[← SION]
[SION adjusts his hiding spot]
[← SAKUYA]
[SAKUYA lets out nothing but a sigh]
This is too scary.
[The seeker appears on the 2nd floor of the practice building]
[Practice building 2F / Seeker / SION / SAKUYA]
Since it looks like the seeker came this way, I’ll turn off the light for a bit.
[← SION / ← Seeker]
[The seeker passes the lab where SION is hiding]
[Sound of the seeker’s cane]
[Slowly getting closer to SAKUYA]
[← SAKUYA]
[The seeker fails to spot SAKUYA behind the shelf]
[Goes upstairs without catching anyone]
Wait a minute.
Does that even make sense?
Why is this so scary?
[Sound of swallowing]
Wait.
I think the seeker is gone.
So they move around making that much noise.
I guess hiding wasn’t the best idea after all.
[SION moves to the lab across the hall]
[Practice building 3F / JAEHEE, RYO, YUSHI]
Hey, what was that sound?
[(Lights off)]
[(Crawling deeper under the desk)]
[← JAEHEE & RYO / YUSHI →]
I’m scared.
[YUSHI →]
[Passes by YUSHI]
[Gets closer to where JAEHEE and RYO are hiding]
[← RYO]
[← JAEHEE]
[Just passes by]
The cane sound got farther away.
[Sound of swallowing]
[(Signal that he survived)]
[The seeker goes back down to the 2nd floor of the practice building]
I hear the cane sound.
[← SION]
[← Seeker]
[Stops in front of the lab SION is hiding]
[Enters the room]
[Starts checking every corner]
Found you! SION!
No...
[Phone notification sound]
[Member SION has been caught and trapped in the confinement room]
SION got caught.
SION doesn’t have that thing.
That... the school supply.
We need to find Sion’s school supply.
[SION’s school supply already found by JAEHEE]
[Heads to the confinement room after reading the message]
Huh? Where is this place?
[SION enters the confinement room]
["Confinement room rules"]
[1. Find the test paper with your name on it and sit down]
[2. Once you're handcuffed, confinement is complete]
So I need the protractor.
Protractor!
[Practice building 3F / RYO / YUSHI / JAEHEE]
I can’t go that way.
[← SAKUYA]
We need to find SION’s.
[SAKUYA doesn't know about the protractor yet]
But what if I go out and
[Struggling with himself]
get caught...
But even if I get caught, I have the eraser, so it’s fine.
Wait x4
Should I go find SION’s school supply?
[(Deep in thought)]
I should go.
It’s okay.
[(Stops)]
Actually, I don’t think this is a good idea.
I really don’t think this is okay.
What even is this?
Maybe I should just die.
Maybe I should just sleep instead.
[← SAKUYA]
The seeker won’t open this, right?
I’m scared.
[RIKU enters the science lab on the 3rd floor of the learning building]
Alright!
[Found a hiding spot]
[Looks outside]
[Sound of the seeker’s cane]
[Quickly hides inside the cabinet]
[RIKU and the seeker are getting closer]
[← Seeker / RIKU →]
I’m scared.
Seriously.
[Stop in front of the science lab]
The seeker is here.
It's here, it's here.
[(Covers mouth)]
[The seeker comes inside]
There’s no one here.
[SUMBAKꓘOKJIL]